subjot.com 2011-12-30

# Privacy Policy

Protecting your privacy and respecting the privacy of others are important aspects of being a good online citizen. Here at Super + Fun, LLC ("Subjot"), we like to practice what we preach; this Privacy Policy describes our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your information. This includes information we may receive when you use the Subjot website, mobile applications, APIs or third-party services ("Services").

## Information Collection and Use

## Registration

In order to post content on Subjot or use other community features, you may need a Subjot account. When you sign up for a Subjot account, you are required to provide some personal information. This information includes a name, a nickname, email address and date of birth. Some of this information, for example, your name and nickname, will be listed publicly on your profile and accessible through our Services. Once you have created an account, you may choose to configure your profile with additional information that will also be publicly displayed, including a website address, a bio, your location and a profile avatar image.

## Your Content

With Subjot, you can easily post and share conversations. By default the conversations you post are publicly accessible through our Services. They are sent to other users who are following you and may be found through our API, RSS feeds, discoverable by search engines and other services.

## Logging

Like most websites, Subjot's servers automatically log certain information when visitors access our Services. These logs may include information such as your IP address, pages visited, browser type and version, referring site and the date and time of the visit.

## Cookies

Cookies are small data files that are stored on your computer by a website and can be accessed by the website when you visit it again. Subjot uses cookies to authenticate users and verify which account they are signed into. Subjot may also use cookies to collect additional usage information to help make product improvements, or set other cookies for safety and security purposes.

## Third Party Services

Our Services may include links or embedded content from third party services, such as pictures, advertisements or usage tracking mechanisms. These services may collect information sent by your browser as a result of accessing them, including the use of cookies and logging of your IP address.

## Disclosure

Subjot only shares non-public personal information with other entities or individuals outside of Subjot in these limited circumstances:

  * When we have your consent to reveal the personal information.
  * We may provide such information to subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purposes of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Subjot, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

Subjot may disclose non-personally identifying, aggregated data, such as usage statistics, the number of visitors to a page or the number of users of our Services.

If Subjot becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any personal information involved in such transactions and provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

## Modifying Your Personal Information

As a registered user, you may modify some of the personal information provided through your Account Settings.

## Our Policy Towards Children

Our services are not directed towards children under the age of 13. If you are the parent or guardian of a child that has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at privacy@Subjot.com. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.

## Changes to this Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at http://Subjot.com/policy.

## Last Modified: May 1, 2011
